Marguerite Higgins Papers
Marguerite Higgins Papers
- Correspondence-subject files
  - Barnet, Sylvan M. Jr., See New York Herald Tribune
  - Baruch, Bernard M. (Box 1)
    See also Navarro, Miss
  - Bates, Ted, See Ted Bates and Company (advertising firm)
  - Beauvoir School (Washington, D.C.) (Box 1)
  - Beblar, Alex (Ambassador), See Yugoslavia (U.N. Delegation from)
  - Beech, Keyes, 2 folders (Box 1)
  - Bell, William G., See Armor Magazine
  - Bellows, Jim, See New York Herald Tribune
  - Bennett, Robert C. (producer) (Box 1)
  - Benson, Ezra T. (Secr. Ag) (Box 1)
  - Bienstock Associates, Inc. (MH's accountant/lawyer) (Box 1)
  - Billings, K. LeMoyne, See Lennen & Newell, Inc. (advertising firm)
  - Birnie, William A. H., See Reader's Digest
  - Black, Creed, See Chicago Daily News
  - Boston Public Library (Box 1)
  - Boston University (Box 1)
  - Bourke-White, Margaret (Box 1)
  - Bowles, Chester (Ambassador) (Box 1)
  - Boyd, Hugh (Box 1)
  - Bradbury, Walter I., See Doubleday & Company, Inc.
  - Bradlee, Benjamin C. (Box 1)
    See also Washington Post
  - Brandt, Willy (Mayor) (Box 1)
    See also Ernst Reuter Society
  - Brazil (Box 1)
  - Bridges, Styles (Senator) (Box 1)
  - British Guiana (Box 1)
  - Brown, Cross & Hamilton (Box 1)
    See also complete list of cross-references at W. Colston Leigh, Inc.
  - Bruce, David (Ambassador), See U.S. Embassy (Great Britain)
  - Buddhism (Box 1)
    See also Vietnam: Buddhists
  - Buddhist-Catholic Riots (Box 1)
  - Bundy, McGeorge (Box 1)
    See also White House, Johnson Administration
  - Bundy, William, See U.S. Department of State
  - Burke, Arleigh (Admiral) (Box 1)
  - Busby, Horace, See White House, Johnson Administration
  - Bye, George T. (literary agent) (Box 1)
  - C, 3 folders (Box 2)
  - Caffrey, Jefferson (Ambassador), See U.S. Embassy (Egypt)
  - Calmer, Ned, See CBS
  - Cambodia (Box 2)
  - Cambodian Embassy (India) (Box 2)
  - Canada (Box 2)
  - Canfield, Cass, See Harper & Row Publishers
  - Cannon, Jimmy (Box 2)
  - Captive Nations (Box 2)
  - Carey, David (Box 2)
    See also Moral Re-armament Center
  - Carlucci, Frank (Box 2)
  - Carpenter, Liz (Box 2)
    See also White House, Johnson Administration; Ladybird Johnson
  - Carroll, Luke P., See New York Herald Tribune
  - Castro, Fidel, See Cuba
  - Cavin, Patty, See Women's National Press Club (Washington, D.C.)
  - CBS (Box 2)
    See also:
    "At Random" (WBBM)
    Curtis Circulation Co.
    "Garry Moore Show" (CBS)
    "Last Word" (CBS)
    "Milwaukee Reports" (WXIX)
    "News Closeups" (KPIX)
    "Small World" (CBS)
    Television and radio appearances fan mail
    "Views of the Press" (WCBS)
  - Chamberlain, John (Box 2)
  - Chase National Bank (New York) (Box 2)
  - Cherne, Leo (Box 2)
  - Chiang Kai-shek (Box 2)
  - Chiang Kai-shek, Madame (Box 2)
  - Chicago Daily News (Box 2)
    See also Beech, Keyes; Lisagor, Peter
  - Chicago Sun-Times (Box 2)
  - China, 3 folders (Box 2)
  - Christian Science Monitor, See Drummond, Roscoe
  - The Christophers (Box 2)
  - Church, Wells, See CBS
  - Churchill, Sir Winston (Box 2)
  - "Cinerama", See Thomas, Lowell
  - Citizens for Freedom, Inc. (New York) (Box 2)
  - Citron, Robert R. (Dr.) (Box 2)
  - Clark, Mark W. (General) (Box 2)
  - Clark, Peter B., See Evening News Association (Detroit)
  - Clay, Lucius D. (General) (Box 2)
  - Clay, Lucius D. (General) - Clay Committee Backgrounder (Box 2)
  - Clemens, Cyril, See International Mark Twain Society
  - Close, Dr. Willliam T. (and "Glennie") (Box 2)
  - Coffey, Raymond R. (Box 2)
  - Cohn, Roy M. (Box 2)
  - Cold War and Communism (Box 2)
  - Cole, Betty (producer), See "Meet the Press" (NBC)
  - Collier, Barnard L.Series, See Clippings - Barnard L. Collier under Dominican Republic
  - Collier's (Box 2)
  - Columbia University School of Journalism (Box 2)
  - Commonweal (Box 2)
  - Compact (Box 2)
  - Congo (Box 2)
  - Coniff, Frank, See Hearst Newspapers; New York Journal American
  - Considine, Bob (Box 2)
  - Consolidated Edison Company of New York, Inc. (Box 2)
  - Constantine, King, See Greece
  - Cooke, Bob, See New York Herald Tribune
  - Copley Press, Inc. (Box 2)
  - Corning Glass International, See Murphy, Robert D. (Ambassador/executive)
  - Corinthian Broadcasting Corporation (New York) (Box 2)
  - Cornish, George A., See New York Herald Tribune
  - Coronet Magazine, See Curtis Circulation Company
  - Cosmopolitan (Box 2)
  - Council of the Revolution Command (Egypt) (Box 2)
    See also Nasser, Gamal Abdel
  - Cousins, Norman and Ellen (Box 2)
    See also Saturday Review
  - Cowles Magazines & Broadcasting, Inc. (Box 2)
    See also Look Magazine
  - Cramer, Ernst J., See Die Welt
  - Crime (Box 2)
  - Critchfield, Richard (Box 2)
  - Cronkite, Walter (Box 2)
  - Cuba, 4 folders (Box 3)
  - Curtis Circulation Company (Box 3)
    See also Ladies Home Journal; Saturday Evening Post
  - Cyprus (Box 3)
  - D (Box 3)
  - Daily Home News (New Brunswick, NJ), See Boyd, Hugh
  - Daily Reporter (Dover, OH) (Box 3)
  - Dallas Times Herald (Box 3)
  - Dang Duc Khoi (Box 3)
  - Dang Sy (Maj.) (Box 3)
    See also O'Connor, Patrick (Fr.)
  - Dang Van Chau (Captain), See Vietnamese Embassy (U.S.)
  - Daniel, Clifton, See New York Times
  - Danish Embassy (U.S.) (Box 3)
  - Davis, Lee, See New York Herald Tribune
  - Davis, Tobé C., See Fashion Division Federation (New York)
  - Dedmon, Emmett, See Chicago Sun-Times
  - Defense, See National Defense and Security
  - De Gasperi, Alcide (Premier) (Box 3)
  - Deich, Werner, See Heine, Dr.
  - Delacorte Press (Box 3)
  - Denson, John L., See New York Herald Tribune
  - Dewey, Thomas E. (Governor) (Box 3)
  - Diplomat (Box 3)
  - Dodd, Thomas (Senator), 2 folders (Box 3)
  - Dominican Republic, 6 folders (Box 3)
  - Donovan, Robert J., See New York Herald Tribune
  - Dooley, Ed, See San Francisco Examiner
  - Dorsey, Thomas B., See New York Herald Tribune
  - Doubleday & Company, Inc.
    - General (Box 4)
      See also Lisagor, Peter
    - Overtime in Heaven - Fan Mail (Box 4)
    - War in Korea - Fan Mail (Box 4)
  - Doubleday Book Shops (Box 4)
  - Douglas, William O. (Supreme Court Justice) (Box 4)
  - Douglas-Hamilton, Malcolm (Lord and Lady), See Citizens for Freedom, Inc.
  - Drake America Corporation (New York) (Box 4)
  - Drummond, Roscoe (Box 4)
    See also Corinthian Broadcasting Corporation
  - Dudman, Richard (Box 4)
  - Duke, Angier Biddle (Box 4)
  - Dulles, Allen W., See U.S. Central Intelligence Agency
  - Dulles, John Foster (Secr.) (Box 4)
    See also U.S. Department of State
  - Dungan, Ralph A., See White House, Johnson Administration
  - Duong Ngoc Lam (General) (Box 4)
  - E (Box 4)
  - East Asia (Box 4)
  - Editions d'Art Lucien Mazenod (Box 4)
  - Egypt, 2 folders (Box 4)
  - Eisenhower, Dwight D. (Box 4)
    See also White House: Eisenhower Administration
  - Engelking, L.L. (Box 4)
    See also New York Herald Tribune
  - Ernst Reuter Society (Box 4)
    See also Brandt, Willy
  - Esty, William, See William Esty Company (advertising firm)
  - Etheridge, Mark, See Newsday
  - Eunson, Bob (Box 4)
  - Europe (Box 4)
  - European Economic Community (Box 4)
  - Evans, Clifford (television moderator/producer), See "Ladies of the Press" (WOR-TV)
  - Evening News Association (Detroit) (Box 4)
  - Evening Star (Washington, D.C.) (Box 4)
  - F (Box 4)
  - Falkenburg, Jinx (radio/television personality) (Box 4)
  - Family Circle (Box 4)
  - Fanning, Lawrence S., See Chicago Daily News
  - Fashion Division Federation (New York) (Box 4)
  - Flannery, W.E. (Hollywood agent) (Box 4)
  - Ford, Gerald R. (Congressman) (Box 4)
  - Ford, Henry (Box 4)
  - Ford Motor Company (Box 4)
  - Foreign Policy, See International Relations
  - Forrest & Lynch (attorneys) (Box 4)
  - France, 2 folders (Box 4)
  - Free Cuba Patriotic Movement (Box 5)
  - Freed, Joe, See New York Herald Tribune
  - Freedom Academy (concept of) (Box 5)
  - Freeman, Lucy (author) (Box 5)
  - Freidin, Seymour, See New York Herald Tribune
  - French Embassy (U.S.), 2 folders (Box 5)
  - French Ministry of Affairs (Box 5)
  - Friedman, Abraham (Box 5)
    See also complete cross-references at W. Colston Leigh, Inc.
  - Friedman, V. E., See V.E. Friedman and Associates
  - Friendly, Alfred, See Washington Post
  - Frings, Kurt (Hollywood agent) (Box 5)
  - "From the People" (RPI) (Box 5)
  - Fuerbringer, Otto, See Time Magazine Inc.
  - Furness, Betty, See "Meet Betty Furness" (NBC)
  - G (Box 5)
  - Gale, Bernays, Falk & Eisner (Box 5)
  - "Garry Moore Show" (CBS) (Box 5)
  - Gavin, James M. (Ambassador), See U.S. Embassy (France)
  - General Headquarters of the Supreme Commander for Allied Powers (GHQ/SCAP) (Box 5)
  - German Embassy (U.S.) (Box 5)
  - Germany, 3 folders (Box 5)
  - Ghanian Embassy (U.S.) (Box 5)
  - Gibbs, Wolcott Jr., See Doubleday & Company, Inc.
  - Gigantes, Gerassimos, See Greece
  - Gillespie, Bob, See Newsday
  - Gilston, Richard, See Delacorte Press
  - Gimbel Brothers (Box 5)
  - Girson, Rochelle, See Saturday Review
  - Glasgow, R. E. (Capt.) (Box 5)
  - Glasgow, Robert H. (Dr.) (Box 5)
  - Göksenin, Muzaffer (General) (Box 5)
  - Goldwater, Barry (Senator) (Box 5)
  - Gould, Bruce, See Ladies Home Journal
  - Gould, Charles, See San Francisco Examiner; Hearst Newspapers
  - Grady, Henry F. (Ambassador) (Box 5)
  - Graham, Katherine, See Washington Post
  - Graham, Philip, See Washington Post
  - Great Britain (Box 5)
    See also British Guiana; U.S. Embassy (Great Britain)
  - Greece (Box 5)
  - Greene, Wallace M. Jr. (General) (Box 5)
  - Greenfield, Jim, See U.S. Department of State
  - Grogan, Stanley (Col.) (Box 5)
  - Grolier Society, Inc. (Box 5)
  - Grubbs, John E., See John E. Grubbs Company (management company)
  - Gruber, Karl (Dr.) (Box 5)
  - Gruenther, Alfred (General), See Supreme Headquarters of the Allied Powers of Europe (SHAPE)
  - Guggenheim, Harry F., See Newsday
  - H (Box 5)
  - Hagerty, James C., See White House: Eisenhower Administration
  - Haitian Embassy (U.S.), See Zephirin, Mauclair
  - Hamilton, Natalie Wales, See Citizens for Freedom, Inc. (New York)
  - Hanoi Radio (Box 5)
  - Harkins, Paul D. (General) (Box 5)
  - Harold Ober Associates (MHs literary agent) (Box 5)
  - Harold R. Peat Incorporated (management firm) (Box 5)
  - Harper & Row Publishers
    - Correspondence, 1951; 1961-1965,; undated; 5 folders (Box 6)
    - Correspondence, Our Vietnam Nightmare, fan mail (Box 6)
  - Harris, Stuart, See Harper & Row Publishers
  - Haywood, O.G. (Box 6)
  - Healy, George F., See Times Picayune (New Orleans)
  - Hearst Newspapers (Box 6)
    See also New York Journal American
  - Hearst, William Jr., See Hearst Newspapers
  - Heath, Donald R. (Ambassador) (Box 6)
  - Heine, Dr. (Box 6)
  - Herter, Christian, See U.S. Department of State
  - Herzberg, Joseph G., See New York Herald Tribune
  - Hickenlooper, Bourke B. (Senator) (Box 6)
  - Hill, I. William, See Evening Star (Washington, D.C.)
  - Hilsman, Roger (Box 6)
  - Hirschhorn, Joseph H. (Box 6)
  - Hoffman, Carl W. (Lt. Col.) (Box 6)
  - Holborn, Fred, See White House: Kennedy Administration
  - Holcomb, Luther (Box 6)
  - Honey, P.J. (Box 6)
  - Hoover, Herbert (Box 6)
  - Houghton Mifflin Co. (Box 6)
    See also North Star Books (Houghton Mifflin Company)
  - Houston Post (Box 6)
  - Howley, Frank L. (Brig. Gen.) (Box 6)
  - Hughes, Emmet J., See Life Magazine
  - Human Events (Box 6)
  - Human Rights (Box 6)
  - Humphrey, George M., See U.S. Department of the Treasury
  - Humphrey, Hubert H. (Senator) (Box 6)
    See also White House: Johnson Administration
  - Hungary (Box 6)
  - Hupp, Charles M., See New York Herald Tribune
  - I (Box 6)
  - Ilma, Viola (Box 6)
  - Indonesia (Republic of) (Box 6)
  - Instructor (Box 6)
  - International Mark Twain Society (Box 6)
  - International Platform Association (Box 6)
  - International Relations (Box 6)
  - Ismay, Lord, See NATO
  - Italian Embassy (U.S.) (Box 6)
  - J (Box 6)
  - J. Leo Kolb Company (MH's insurance and real estate agency) (Box 6)
  - Jackson, C.D., See White House: Eisenhower Administration
  - Jackson, Henry M. (Senator) (Box 6)
  - Jackson, William H. S (Box 6)
  - Jakes, John (Box 6)
  - Japan (Box 6)
  - Jensen, Bob, See White House: Johnson Administration
  - John E. Grubbs & Company (management company) (Box 6)
  - Johnson, Ladybird, See White House: Johnson Administration
  - Johnson, Lyndon B., See White House: Johnson Administration
  - Johnson, R. W. (Johnson & Johnson) (Box 6)
  - Jones, Howard P., See U.S. Embassy (Taiwan); U.S. Embassy (Indonesia)
  - Jones, Robert Letts, See Copley Press, Inc.
  - Jones, W. Alton (Box 6)
  - Judd, Walter H. (Senator) (Box 6)
  - Juhn, Kurt, See Neue Illustrierte (New Illustrated)
  - Juster, Eve. D., See New York Herald Tribune
  - K (Box 6)
  - Kahn's Department Store (Oakland, CA) (Box 6)
  - Karayn, Jim (producer), See National Educational Television and Radio Center (NET)
  - Keating, Kenneth B. (Senator) (Box 6)
  - Keedick Lecture Bureau, Inc.
    See also Lecture and speech material
    - Itineraries (Box 7)
    - Publicity (Box 7)
    - Reviews (Box 7)
  - Keller, James (Fr.), See The Christophers
  - Kelley, Frank, See New York Herald Tribune
  - Kennedy, Edward (Box 7)
  - Kennedy, Ethel (Mrs. Robert F.) (Box 7)
  - Kennedy, Jackie (Box 7)
    See also White House: Kennedy Administration
  - Kennedy, John F. (Box 7)
  - Kennedy, Robert F. (Box 7)
  - Kennedy, Rose (Box 7)
  - Kent, Joanne (MH's secretary) (Box 7)
  - Kerr, Walter B., See New York Herald Tribune
  - King Features Syndicate (Box 7)
    See also Rogers, Lela B. (Ginger Rogers' mother/agent)
  - Knight, Ralph, See Saturday Evening Post
  - Knowland, William F. (Senator) (Box 7)
  - Kolb, J. Leo, See J. Leo Kolb Company
  - Korea - POWs (Box 7)
  - Korean Embassy (U.S.) (Box 7)
  - Korean War (Box 7)
  - KPIX (San Francisco), See "News Closeups" (KPIX)
  - Krock, Arthur (Box 7)
    See also New York Times
  - Krulak, Victor H. (General) (Box 7)
  - L (Box 7)
  - Ladies' Home Journal (Box 7)
  - "Ladies of the Press" (WOR-TV) (Box 7)
  - Laird, Melvin R. (Congressman) (Box 7)
  - Lamborn, Robert See Left Wing Politics (Box 7)
  - Land, Frank S. (Box 7)
  - Landry, R.B. (Major General) (Box 7)
  - Lansdale, Edward G. (General) (Box 7)
  - Lasky, Melvin J. (Box 7)
  - "Last Word" (CBS) (Box 7)
  - Latin America, 3 folders (Box 7)
  - Lawrence, David, See U.S. News & World Report
  - Lectures and Speech Materials (Box 7)
    See also Keedick Lecture Bureau, Inc.
  - Left Wing Politics (Box 8)
    See also Tocsin; University of California, Berkeley
  - Legation of Switzerland (U.S.) (Box 8)
  - Leigh, W. Colston, See W. Colston Leigh, Inc.
  - Lendvai, Paul (journalist/author) (Box 8)
  - Lennen & Newell, Inc. (advertising firm) (Box 8)
  - Leonhart, William (Ambassador), See U.S. Embassy (Tanzania)
  - Lequerica, Jose F. de, See Spanish Embassy (U.S.)
  - Levin, Carl (Box 8)
    Arnstein, Helen M. (Mrs. Joseph)
    Evening Star (Washington, D.C.)
    El Mundo
    Munroe, Pat
    Newsday correspondence between Feb.-Apr. 1965
    Polanco-Albreu, Santiago
    Spencer, George
    Townley, Updike, Carter & Rodgers
  - Life (Box 8)
    See also Mydans, Carl
  - Limpus, Lowell M., See New York Daily News
  - Lincoln, Evelyn, See White House: Kennedy Administration
  - Lippmann, Walter (Box 8)
  - Lipscomb, Glenard P. (Congressman) (Box 8)
  - Lisagor, Peter (Box 8)
    See also Chicago Daily News; Doubleday & Company, Inc.; Pulitzer Prize; Saturday Evening Post
  - Lodge, Henry Cabot Jr. (Ambassador) (Box 8)
    See also U.S. Mission to the United Nations
  - Look (Box 8)
    See also Cowles Magazine & Broadcasting, Inc.
  - Lucas, Jim (Box 8)
  - Luce, Clare Booth (Box 8)
    See also National Review
  - M (Box 8)
  - MacArthur, Douglas (General) (Box 8)
  - MacArthur, Jean (Mrs. Douglas) (Box 8)
  - MacDuffie, Marshall (Box 8)
  - MacKenna, Kenneth (actor) (Box 8)
  - Mademoiselle (Box 8)
  - Manning Public Relations Firm (New York) (Box 8)
  - Mansfield, Mike (Senator) (Box 8)
  - Marlens, Al, See Newsday
  - Mathias, Charles McC. Jr. (Senator) (Box 8)
  - Maury, Jack (Box 8)
  - Maxon, Inc. (advertising firm, New York) (Box 8)
  - Mayes, Herbert R., See McCalls
  - Malaysia (Box 8)
  - Mayor, Joe (Box 8)
    See also O'Connor, Patrick (Father)
  - MCA (Box 8)
    See also Musicor (record company); Paramount Studios
  - McCabe, Ralph (Scott Paper Co.) (Box 8)
  - McCaffrey, Neil, See Arlington House Publishers
  - McCalls (Box 8)
  - McCormick, Kenneth D., See Doubleday & Company, Inc.
  - McKinney, Don, See Saturday Evening Post
  - McKnight, Felix, See Dallas Times Herald
  - McManus, Robert C. (Box 8)
  - McManus, Robert L. (Box 8)
  - McNamara, Francis J. (Box 8)
  - Mecklin, John, See Time Magazine Inc.
  - "Meet Betty Furness" (NBC) (Box 8)
  - "Meet the Press" (NBC), 2 folders (Box 8)
  - Menshikov, Mikhail (Ambassador), See Soviet Embassy (U.S.)
  - Metropolitan Broadcasting Corporation (MBC) (Box 8)
    See also "Opinion in the Capital" (MBC)
  - Michaelis, J. H. (Lt. General) (Box 8)
  - Migonis Secretarial Service (employed by MH) (Box 8)
  - Miller, Hope Ridings (Box 8)
    See also Diplomat; New York Herald Tribune
  - "Milwaukee Reports" (WXIX) (Box 8)
  - Mohammed Reza Shah Pahlevi (Shah of Iran) (Box 8)
  - Montgomery, Ruth (Box 8)
  - Moore, Garry (talk show host), See "Garry Moore Show" (CBS)
  - Moore, Joseph H. (Lt. General) (Box 8)
  - Moral Re-armament Center (note "Glennie Close") (Michigan) (Box 8)
  - Morgan, Penny, See CBS
  - Morris, Wayne (Senator) (Box 8)
  - Mossadegh, Gollem (Dr.) (Box 8)
  - Mossadegh, Mohammed (Prime Minister) (Box 8)
  - Moyers, Bill, See White House: Johnson Administration
  - El Mundo (Box 8)
  - Munroe, Pat (Box 8)
  - Munson, Marguerite, See Harper & Row Publishers
  - Murphy, Robert D. (Ambassador/executive) (Box 8)
  - Murrow, Edward R. (Box 8)
  - Musicor (record company, later MCA) (Box 8)
  - Mydans, Carl (photographer) (Box 8)
  - N (Box 9)
  - NASA (Box 9)
    See also U.S. Space Program; Soviet Union
  - Nasser, Gamel Abdel (President) (Box 9)
  - National Catholic Welfare Conference (NCWC) (Box 9)
    See also Dang Sy (Maj.); O'Connor, Patrick (Fr.)
  - National Defense and Security, 2 folders (Box 9)
    See also Nuclear Weapons; U.S. Congress: National Defense and Security
  - National Education Association (Washington, D.C.) (Box 9)
  - National Educational Television and Radio Center (NET) (Box 9)
  - National Review (Box 9)
    See also Luce, Clare Booth
  - NATO, 2 folders (Box 9)
  - Navarro, Miss (Box 9)
    See also Baruch, Bernard M.
  - NBC (Box 9)
    John E. Grubbs & Company, Inc.
    "Meet Betty Furness" (NBC)
    "Meet the Press" (NBC)
    "Today" (NBC)
    "Youth Wants to Know" (NBC)
  - Netherlands Embassy (U.S.) (Box 9)
  - Neue Illustrierte (New Illustrated) (Box 9)
  - Newman, Joe (Box 9)
  - New York Daily News (Box 9)
  - New York Herald Tribune
    - Correspondence, 1943; 1950-1965,; undated; 4 folders (Box 9)
    - Fan mail, 1950-1964; undated; 3 folders (Box 9)
  - New York Journal American (Box 9)
    See also Hearst Newspapers
  - New York Times (Box 9)
  - New York World's Fair (1964-1965) Corp. (Box 9)
  - "News Closeups" (KPIX) (Box 9)
  - Newsday
    - Correspondence, 1963 (Box 10)
    - Correspondence, 1964; 4 folders (Box 10)
    - Correspondence, 1965; 4 folders (Box 10)
    - Correspondence, undated (Box 10)
    - Fan Mail, 1963 (Box 10)
    - Fan Mail, 1964; 2 folders (Box 10)
    - Fan Mail, 1965; 2 folders (Box 10)
    - Fan Mail, undated (Box 10)
  - Newsweek (Box 10)
  - Ngo Dinh Nhu (Box 10)
  - Ngo Dinh Nhu, Madame, 2 folders (Box 10)
    See also Tran Van Chuong (Ambassador); Tran Van Chuong, Madame
  - Nguyen Cao Ky (Premier) (Box 11)
  - Nguyen Dinh Thuan (Box 11)
  - Nguyen Huu Long (Box 11)
  - Nguyen Khac Tan (Box 11)
  - Nguyen Khanh (General) (Box 11)
  - Nguyen Van Huan (Box 11)
  - Nguyen ? Thi (Col.) (Box 11)
  - Nicolai, Leon (Box 11)
  - Nixon, Richard M. (Box 11)
  - Nolting, Frederick E. Jr. (Ambassador) (Box 11)
  - Nong Kimny (Ambassador), See Cambodian Embassy (India)
  - North Star Books (Houghton Mifflin Company) (Box 11)
  - North, Sterling, See North Star Books (Houghton Mifflin Company)
  - Norway (Box 11)
  - Norwegian Embassy (U.S.) (Box 11)
  - Noyes, Crosby, See Evening Star (Washington, D.C.)
  - Noyes, Crosby S. (Box 11)
  - Noyes, Newbold (Newby), See Evening Star (Washington, D.C.)
  - Nuclear Weapons (Box 11)
    See also National Defense and Security; Soviet Union
  - O (Box 11)
  - Ober, Harold, See Harold Ober Associates (MH's literary agent)
  - O'Connor, Patrick (Fr.), 2 folders (Box 11)
    Buddhism
    Buddhist-Catholic Riots
    Dang Sy (Maj.)
    Mayor, Joe
    National Catholic Welfare Conference (NCWC)
    Reed, John
    Vietnam-Buddhists
  - O'Leary, Jeremiah, See Evening Star (Washington, D.C.)
  - O'Neill, Michael, See Mayor, Joe; New York Daily News
  - "Opinion in the Capital" (MBC) (Box 11)
  - Ottenberg, Miriam, See Evening Star (Washington, D.C.), Women's National Press Club
  - Overseas Press Club of America (Box 11)
  - P (Box 11)
  - Panama (Box 11)
  - Papathanasiades (General), See Greece
  - Paramount Studios (Box 11)
    See also MCA
  - Parton, Margaret, See New York Herald Tribune
  - Peat, Harold R., See Harold R. Peat Incorporated (management firm)
  - Peck, Marshall, See Newsday
  - Perfect Home (magazine), See STAMATS Publishing Company
  - Perlberg, Bill (producer), See MCA; Paramount Studios
  - Peterman, Cy, See Human Events
  - Pham Ngoc Thao (General) (Box 11)
  - Philadelphia Inquirer (Box 11)
  - Pittsburgh Press (Box 11)
  - Polanco-Albreau, Santiago (Box 11)
  - Poland (Box 11)
  - Portugal (Box 11)
  - Postel, Diana D. (MH's secretary) (Box 11)
  - Presbyterian Hospital (NYC) (Box 11)
  - Price, Raymond K. Jr., See New York Herald Tribune
  - Puerto Rico (Box 11)
  - Pulitzer Prize (Box 11)
  - R (Box 11)
  - Radio Press International (RPI), See "From the People" (RPI)
  - Reader's Digest (Box 11)
  - Reap, Joe (Box 11)
  - Reed, John (Box 11)
  - Reedy, George, See White House: Johnson Administration
  - Reid, Helen, See New York Herald Tribune
  - Reid, Ogden R., See New York Herald Tribune
  - Reid, Whitlaw (Whitie), See New York Herald Tribune
  - Report (magazine) (Box 11)
  - Reston, James, See New York Times
  - Reuther, Walter P. (Box 11)
  - Rhee, Syngman (President) (Box 11)
  - Rhodes, Robert E., See Newsday
  - Ridgeway, Matthew B. (General) (Box 11)
  - R.J. Reynolds Tobacco Co., See William Esty Company
  - Roberts, Juanita, See White House: Johnson Administration; White House: Kennedy Administration
  - Rockefeller, Nelson A. (Governor) (Box 11)
  - Rogers, Ginger, See Rogers, Lela B.
  - Rogers, Lela B. (Ginger Rogers' mother/agent) (Box 11)
    See also King Features Syndicate
  - Rosen, Lucie Bigelow (Box 11)
  - Rosenstein, Nettie (jewelry designer), See Fashion Division Federation (New York)
  - Rostow, Walter, See White House: Johnson Administration
  - Round Hill Developments, Ltd. (Jamaica), 2 folders (Box 11)
  - Rountree, Martha (talk show host), See "Meet the Press" (NBC)
  - Rowan, Carl T., See U.S. Information Agency
  - Ruder & Finn Incorporated (public relations) (Box 11)
  - Rusk, Dean (Secr.), See U.S. Department of State
  - Russia, See Soviet Union
  - Ryan, Cornelius, See Collier's
  - S (Box 12)
  - Saga (magazine) (Box 12)
  - Saltonstall, Leverett (Senator) (Box 12)
  - San Francisco Examiner (Box 12)
  - Sandborn, Phil, See Newsday
  - Sargeant, Dwight D., See New York Herald Tribune
  - Saturday Evening Post (Box 12)
  - Saturday Review (Box 12)
  - Scharper, Philip, See Commonweal
  - Scherbatov, Adelaide (Princess) (Box 12)
  - Schlesinger, Arthur Jr., See White House: Kennedy Administration
  - Schlichting, Günter, See Die Welt am Sonntag